My name is **Vincent Navetat**. I have become a UX Designer after 6 years of experience in Web development.

I work through the full UX lifecycle from research to design testing utilising all elements of a user-centered design process to create innovative cross-platform experiences. call write visit meet +44 7523 788219 vincentnavetat@gmail.com vincentnavetat.github.io London N1, UK

Skillset

User Research:

Competitor analysis, surveys, interviews, card sorting, task models

Solution Design:

Personas, storyboards, sketching, wireframing, interaction design, prototyping, user journeys

Usability Testing:

Tree testing, focus groups, lab testing, A/B testing

UX Tools:

Adobe XD, MyBalsamiq, UXPin Photoshop, Illustrator SurveyMonkey, Optimizely

Web Development:

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, PostCSS Mobile-first Responsive Web Design Javascript, jQuery, Grunt/Gulpjs PHP5/MySQL, OOP Git, SVN WordPress, Drupal, eZ Publish Agile methodologies (Scrum, Kanban)

Education

CareerFoundry

UX Design Course 2016

University Paris-Est Marne-la-Vallée

Diplôme d'Ingénieur IMAC $2006 \rightarrow 2009$ Equivalent to Master's Degree in Computer Science applied to Arts, Communication and Entertainment

University Clermont-Ferrand II

DUT Services et Réseaux de Communication 2004 → 2006

Equivalent to Bachelor's Degree in Multimedia and Communication

Languages

English - Fluent French - Native Spanish - Notions

Experience



London
Dec 2014 → Present

Senior Front-End Developer

I have worked within the UX/UI team to develop corporate websites and user interfaces for IRIS cloud applications. I created new features, maintained and refactored codebases and optimised pageload performances.

I ensured the use of the latest front-end techniques and advocated for user experience best practices. I participated in the hiring and mentoring processes of

I participated in the hiring and mentoring projunior developers.



London
Oct 2012 → Dec 2014

Full-Stack Web Developer

I developed and maintained websites for clients such as The Financial Times, The French National Healthcare, Energy Saving Trust, etc.

I defined project technical specifications, ensured cross-browser/device compatibility and handled client communication.

SMARTT

Vancouver $Mar 2011 \rightarrow Sep 2012$

Full-Stack Web Developer

I worked on the development of connectthedoc.com, a booking platform for medical appointments in Canada. I developed Drupal and WordPress websites and trained website administrators.

I received training in UX Design (delivered by Habanero Consulting Group) and Account Management.

maecia

Paris
Apr 2009 → Jan 2011

Front-End Web Developer

I converted designs from PSD to XHTML/CSS/Javascript and developed eZ Publish websites for clients such as Publicis Consultants, The French Ministry of Food and Agriculture, Louis Berger Group, etc.

You can find my professional recommendations on http://linkedin.com/in/vincentnavetat

Hobbies and interests









